PENNY:
So,
(Penny:)Dan, you have a grandson.
How old is he?
(Dan:)Seven.
BERNADETTE:
Oh, yeah.
(Bernadette:)I remember him from the picnic.
(Bernadette:)He was the one crying
like a wuss the whole time.
(Penny:)I heard he was being picked on
by a mean kid.
(Bernadette:)Just builds character.
(Bernadette:)Like my dad said,
"Nobody likes a crybaby
(Bernadette:)except their mommies
and Democrats."
(Dan:)I need another drink.
(Bernadette:)What's his problem?
Oh.
(Raj:)I don't know.
Maybe he didn't like the fact
(Penny:)that you called his grandson
a wuss.
(Bernadette:)Well, I didn't think you were
supposed to say "sissy" anymore.
(Penny:)Okay, look, I know
what a good person you are,
(Penny:)but sometimes people think you
might come off a little harsh.
(Bernadette:)What?
(Bernadette:)I'm, like, the sweetest person
I know.
(Bernadette:)Look at me. I should be
in a tree baking cookies.
(Penny:)Yes, but once in a while,
(Penny:)people think
you're a little mean.
(Dan:)Oh, yeah?